LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
I'm a soldier - that means I'm
Both a defendant and the judge
I am standing on both ends of the flame
Rounding curves
Overtaking life and death,
I run and fight with false shadows
No matter how many threads of
deception are woven together,
The truth shall illuminate the face of light
Save your tears for the day
when our pain is far behind
on your feet, come with me
We are soldiers stand or die
Save your fears, take your place
Save them for the judgement day
fast and free, follow me
Time to make the sacrifice.
We rise or fall
Prime Minister Kayabuki has just welcomed
Secretary of State Schroeder with a handshake.
The American Empire has been demonstrating its authority
as a military state since the last great war.
However, as it now suffers
from a collapsed economy,
Japan is taking the initiative in seeking a common
ground for the renegotiation of the security pact
by inviting the Secretary of State to
its territory, in a strong-arm tactic.
However, since the Japanese government also
suffers from many serious domestic problems
such as an unstable economy,
delays in refugee policy, and the Article 9 issue,
the intensification of protests
from many areas is unavoidable.
You shouldn't watch that crap, even during a break!
Don't take it out on them
just because you're losing.
Hey, look who's talking.
This time, it's all me.
I don't think so.
Beware the
Left Eye
Hey, hey. Why do we still have to
bother with security relationships?
Japan has a military, doesn't it?
The current regime is very hawkish,
but since the American
Empire's economy is battered,
they'd like to renew the security pact
now, while they have the upper hand.
I guess they want to redeem themselves for the
humiliation they suffered during the last century.
What humiliation?
Well, to put it simply, they lost the war.
Besides, there's that uncertain item in the Constitution
known as Article 9, which is still in effect.
meaning that the Self-Defence Force
can't take preemptive actions overseas
and that they can't have nuclear weapons.
The last security pact made in the
previous century functioned well,
despite the fact that the agreement was
reached at the cost of Japan's pride,
due to the tacit agreement that America should
function as the sword and Japan as the shield.
But now that a new enemy,
the economy, has come into view,
this new agreement is based on the two countries
wanting to cover each other's weaknesses, I bet.
Wow, you're really mature.
Let me synchronise with that data.
Sure, I don't mind.
I said, shut up.
That's right. This is a serious game.
Stay quiet.
Aw, not you too, Azuma-kun!
Aren't you being a bit
too cocky for a newcomer?
Don't take it out on others
just because you're losing.
Dammit.
I'll turn the tables on you.
I raise.
I'll raise, too.
That's the ticket.
When it comes down to it,
poker is a game of chance;
why does Saitou-San always win?
That's been bothering me for a while, too.
In particular, under the current rules of the game,
all you have to do is to memorise everyone's cards
and predict their hand from
their first and last cards.
Saitou-San shouldn't be winning every time,
but for some reason,
he takes all the chips in the end.
He's just good at bluffing.
I'll tear that front of yours down soon enough.
Yeah, he's right.
It's called having a poker face.
Remember that.
You guys can't do it.
Compared to the game of life and
death, poker is child's play.
Touché
I'll acknowledge that
you're a top notch sniper,
but comparing poker to sniping
still won't hold water.
Once, I was in a one-on-one sniping duel
with someone who had me scared shitless.
I'd never feared a battle of
wits as I did in that match.
Ever since that match,
I've been able to predict
the thoughts of most people
with a single glance.
I find that hard to believe.
By the way, what kind of
opponent was that person?
You want me to tell?
I do!
I'll talk if everyone calls me.
It's not that I want to hear your story.
Don't get me wrong.
It was in the summer of 2020.
Eurasia was preoccupied with
a futile war of attrition.
I was sick of Japan,
which was enjoying an extra-punitive
isolationist policy amidst
the strange political balance.
I'd joined the Red Bianco as a mercenary,
a volunteer corps supporting
the interim Mexican government.
At the time, my left eye was still
safe and sound in its socket,
Oil from the Middle East,
drugs from South America:
conflict is a given in areas
where a vested interest arises.
The American Empire, divided and
exhausted from the previous world war,
was beginning to seriously consider
eradicating the new continent's drug market
to prevent the outflow of their national budget.
Under the pretext of overthrowing
the corrupt Mexican government,
the American Empire incited the United Nations
to deploy the UN troops, consisting of British
and Japanese forces, to South America.
First, citing expedited capture
of the capital as a reason,
they pushed through carpet-bombing.
Later, they resorted to deploying mechanised troops
to Monterrey to sweep up the remaining guerillas.
All my comrades were eliminated by the
UN mechanised troops after the bombing.
Judging that it was time to call it quits,
I was waiting for a chance to surrender.
It was at that time...
that a terminal that had been
monitoring enemy communications
reported that it had discovered enemy special ops
troops in possession of a tactical nuclear device.
Not having accomplished much
of note in battle until then,
I thought I should work for my
pay in return for the thrill.
I truly meant to rain terror down on these
bastards from God's own vantage point,
since they had shown that they had the
gall to bring a nuclear device into play.
Something wrong?
No. It's nothing.
That must be it.
They're too concerned about criticism of
attacks on medical organisations and churches;
there are too many remaining nests
where the guerillas may lurk.
True.
But there should be two platoons who
are sweeping the surviving forces.
I'd hope that's the case.
You guys aren't thorough enough in general.
Aren't you Brits worshipping the
SAS legend a bit too much as well?
He thinks he's fucking John Rambo.
Bit start.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Sniper!
Get down!
Ishikawa, assume that the sniper
is using a satellite feed.
Hack the satellite and
determine the enemy's location.
Understood.
Why...
Dammit...
Corporal Mother, please stay still!
He's not using a satellite feed.
A long-range jammer is active
within a one-kilometre radius.
Can you determine the enemy's location by
tracing the jammer's transmission point?
I'm on it already.
You guys are efficient.
Are you veterans?
If you have time for chit-chat,
go scout for enemies,
you rookie.
Which direction did he shoot from?!
Were you able to confirm?!
The enemy will hear us!
Switch to cyberbrain comm systems!
Try it.
You'll be surprised at the white noise.
Dammit.
We messed up.
We couldn't find the enemy at all.
We have to treat him as soon as possible.
Hey, what now, Sergeant?!
Ginger, everyone will cover for you.
Get Mother out of there.
Snow, help Ginger.
Damn racist bastard.
Hey, you Japs!
Target the west buildings!
The rest, target the east buildings!
Let's go!
Don't worry. You'll be all right.
Think you can make it?
Okay!
Dammit!
He's in a west building!
I'll have to make you guys wonder
where I am for a bit longer.
Shit in your pants.
A 20mm!
Wait, stop shooting!
Stop!
From which direction was Ginger shot?
The west.
What are you talking about?
Didn't you see the car get blown up just now?!
The sniper's in the east!
No, it's more than likely we're surrounded!
Ishikawa, did you figure out
where the jamming's coming from?
Rough estimates, but I have three spots.
One's in an east building.
The other two would be the
church and the hospital.
Do you think the one in the
east building is a decoy?
Probably.
Before the 20mm was fired, the jamming
signal disappeared for a split second.
Besides, it's basic strategy
to put the sun at your back.
Sergeant!
The shot from the east is probably
a decoy; there's no one there!
If we're surrounded, we'd be getting more shots.
It may be that there is only one sniper.
How the hell can you be sure?
That's what the situation indicates.
I have a suggestion.
I'll go over to your side after
passing through the east building.
I will signal you once I have
confirmed that the building is empty.
Once I give the signal, everyone will fire
at will at the church and the hospital.
Use the opportunity to retrieve the
Corporal and the tactical nuclear device.
Without it, we're stuck here.
All right, go with Snow!
Meeting up via a detour, huh?
They'll know soon enough that there
is no one in the east building.
Before that happens...
I'll take out someone else.
As we'd suspected.
Don't move, Mother!
There was no one, as we'd suspected.
There was only one round, too.
He's a smart one.
But there is probably only one of him;
we'll get him with our superior numbers.
All right, the sniper is in the church.
We'll bring him down!
No, he could be in the hospital.
Even if we excluded the other abandoned buildings,
because the jamming signal was cut
and we can't confirm a transmitter.
we can't totally dismiss the
hospital as a possible location.
How many metres away do you think the hospital is?!
He's in the church!
How can you be sure?!
He's a sniper who challenges us while
making sure the GPS can't be used.
If he's a veteran fighter versed even
in the Coriolis effect,
we'll all get killed!
Too complicated.
Who gives a damn which one it is?
Be patient.
Caution, not bravery, is the key to
survival on the battlefield.
Take a good look at that female gorilla.
That's who you'd call a real pro.
"Female gorilla"?
A woman?
Pickles!
Got him!
The enemy's in the hospital!
Ishikawa!
Bastard!
In any case, we've retrieved the pod.
We were too late for the Corporal.
All right, let's retreat for now.
We can't all die here.
You're joking.
Pickles got killed!
We've gotta avenge him.
Let's get the guy!
That's an order!
We retreat now, and regroup!
A retreat is fine, but either way,
we'll need to fight the sniper.
We can't call for reinforcements as
long as our comm systems are out.
Yeah, that's right.
We still have the numerical advantage.
What are you going to do?
Your buddies were killed, too!
All right, let's do it.
Something's wrong.
They didn't panic. They're regrouping.
They must have a good commanding officer.
I realised that the final battle was drawing near.
The tension shot up,
and I could feel my adrenaline
level rising on a cellular level.
When you kill each other on the battlefield,
you can't tell who killed whom.
But there is one exception to this rule,
and that would be snipers.
The very act of sniping has a name attached to it from the outset.
That's why snipers can't become POWs.
As the hated enemy who killed their
buddies and commanding officers,
snipers are fated to be killed on the spot.
Once you put a recoilless round in
there, pump it full of smoke rounds!
We'll mount an assault under cover of the smoke!
All right!
Damn Bastard!
Okay, cover me!
Snow and I will be in the assault!
Damn, I have to be backup?
Congrats.
You got her trust.
Dammit.
That's enough.
Leave the rest to the Major.
She'll manage the rest.
The "Major"?
What's up with her,
being called female gorilla and shit?
Who the hell is she?
I have no idea.
But she's a genius at combat,
and we call her "Major".
Upon confronting the Major, in that
moment that was less than a second,
I imagined the conclusion
and felt a chill of fear.
It was a conclusion that my
experience as a sniper arrived at
after considering all possible
variables and circumstances.
"I will be killed."
From her stance, the way she held the
rifle at her waist and didn't even blink,
I immediately understood that
she was a complete cyborg.
In addition, her rifle was a
full-sensing semi-automatic.
She would then of course have targeting control
systems for long, medium, and short ranges installed.
I tried firing one shot at
the Major in my imagination.
The Major will shoot down my first shot;
I, with my bolt action rifle, will get hit with her second
shot while trying to re-conceal myself behind the pillar.
No matter how many times I ran
the simulation, it was the same.
But, but!
You couldn't let that situation continue!
Yeah.
If I had let the situation continue,
I would've eventually been killed anyway.
I desperately tried to think
of how I could turn the tables.
Then, I noticed something.
It was the jamming equipment
that the Major first shot.
Why did the Major destroy this first,
even using three shots to do it?
"Wait, could it be that she doesn't have a
medium-distance targeting software installed?"
"Yes, that must be it."
"Even though she is a sniper,
she had her full-sensing rifle use a short barrel."
"That is because she has decided to have the rifle
act as a sub-machine gun at medium distances."
"If so, to snipe at this medium distance,
she needs the targeting software."
"Is she in the middle of downloading the
targeting software from the satellite?"
You have good skills.
Join my command.
From the very beginning, you...
Yes, I was deceived by the Major's
poker face from the very beginning.
I had no right to refuse;
that was her first order to me, after all.
Deal me my last card.
That was an interesting story,
but it has nothing to do with this game.
I'm all in!
I call.
Don't play tough.
This time, you can't bluff your way through.
You're going for a royal flush of spades, right?
But you've got rags.
I know, because I have the ace of spades.
You have no chance of winning.
Besides, that story right
now was a lie too, wasn't it?
it was an interesting story,
but there was an old movie that had a similar plot.
Yeah, that's right.
I made it all up.
What? Really?!
I'll let you guys go for today.
Azuma, cash me out, okay?
Got embarrassed, huh?
Hey, rookie, I want it all in advance.
You're one demanding senpai.
I wonder if Saitou-San really had rags.
Hey everyone, look!
Saitou-San had a straight
flush with a nine of spades!
What'd you say?
Then, that story just now...
could be true...
Could be...
Finding out a galaxy
of planets and stars within me.
Listening to each of them
singing the same silent melody.
I've never seen such beauty
in possibility...
No smack of doubt or fear.
(Wake up)
I hear a voice.
(And show the light)
hear a voice calling out to me.
(Wake up)
I see inside (Our time is now)
see the light now ever holding me.
All the truth,
(All the truth) All I need,
to make all this reality.
(it's inside)
The beauty within the shell.
(deep within the shell)
(within the shell)
(Wake up)
I hear a voice (And show the light)
hear a voice calling out to me.
(Wake up)
I see inside, (the time is now)
see the light now ever holding me.
All the truth,
(All the truth) All I need,
to make all this reality,
it's inside
right here within this shell.